Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes, 47643
  - Phillpotts, Eden (1862-1960): Correspondence to Mr. Savage, undated; 48992 (Box 137, Folder 23)
  - Phillpotts, Eden (1862-1960): Miscellaneous, undated; 48991 (Box 137, Folder 24)
  - Phillpotts, Eden (1862-1960): MSS. The Devil and the Deep Sea; Biography; Reveillie; Untitled, undated; 48990 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  - Phipps, Charles Beamont, Sir (1801-1866); Piatt, John James (1835-1917); Pierce, Lorne Albert (1890-1961), undated; 48989 (Box 137, Folder 26)
  - Pierpont, John (1785-1866), undated; 48988 (Box 137, Folder 27)
  - Pike, James Albert (1913- ); Pike, Marshall Spring, undated; 48987 (Box 137, Folder 28)
  - [Pindar, Peter: see Wolcot, John, Box 191], 1690-2000; 48986 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_08df82342959325ccf2d9ae7a98d622d)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): 1884-1910, 48985 (Box 137, Folder 29)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): 1911-1932, 48984 (Box 137, Folder 30)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Amazons, 1893; 48983 (Box 137.2, Folder 1)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Benefit of the Doubt, 1895; 48982 (Box 137.2, Folder 2)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Enchanted Cottage, 1921; 48981 (Box 137.2, Folder 3)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Freaks, 1918; 48980 (Box 137.4, Folder 1)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Gay Lord Quex, 1899; 48979 (Box 137.4, Folder 2)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): Girls and Boys, 1880; 48978 (Box 137.4, Folder 3)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Hobby Horse, Act 1, 1886; 48977 (Box 137.6, Folder 1)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Hobby Horse, Acts 2 & 3, 1886; 48976 (Box 137.6, Folder 2)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): Iris, 1901; 48975 (Box 137.6, Folder 3)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): Letty, 1903; 48974 (Box 137.6, Folder 4)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): Low Water, 1882; 48973 (Box 137.6, Folder 5)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Money Spinner, 1880; 48972 (Box 137.6, Folder 6)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): Quick Work, 1919; 48971 (Box 137.8, Folder 1)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Rocket, 1883; 48970 (Box 137.8, Folder 2)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The School Mistress, 1886; 48969 (Box 137.8, Folder 3)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): Sweet Lavender, 1887; 48968 (Box 137.8, Folder 4)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): The Second Mrs. Tangueray, 1893; 48967 (Box 137.8, Folder 5)
  - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir (1855-1934): A Wife without a Smile, 1904; 48966 (Box 137.8, Folder 6)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from A - B, undated; 48965 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from C - D, undated; 48964 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from E - F, undated; 48963 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from G, undated; 48962 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from H - J, undated; 48961 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from L, undated; 48960 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from M, undated; 48959 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from N - P, undated; 48958 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from R, undated; 48957 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from S, undated; 48956 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from T - V, undated; 48955 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from W, undated; 48954 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Pinker, James B. [literary agent]: Correspondence from [unidentified], undated; 48953 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Pinkerton, John (1758-1826), undated; 48952 (Box 139, Folder 1a)
  - Piozzi, Hester Lynch (1741-1821), undated; 48951 (Box 139, Folder 1b)
  - Pitt-Taylor, Nora, undated; 48950 (Box 139, Folder 2a)
  - Platt, Arthur, undated; 48949 (Box 139, Folder 2b)
  - Planche´, James Robinson (1796-1880), undated; 48948 (Box 139, Folder 2c)
  - Playfair, Lyon, baron (1816-1898), undated; 48947 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Playfair, Nigel Ross (1874-1934), undated; 48946 (Box 139, Folder 2e)
  - Plimmer, B. Helena, undated; 48945 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Plumptre, Annabella, undated; 48944 (Box 139, Folder 3a)
  - Plumptre, Edward (Hayes) (1821-1891), undated; 48943 (Box 139, Folder 3b)
  - Poe, Edgar Allen: [includes photocopies of Robins Archive letters], undated; 48942 (Box 139, Folder 4a)
  - Pocock, Doris A., undated; 48941 (Box 139, Folder 4b)
  - Poggendorf, Johann Christian (1796-1877), undated; 48940 (Box 139, Folder 5a)
  - Pollock, Channing (1880- ), undated; 48939 (Box 139, Folder 5b)
  - Pond, Frederick Eugene (1856-1925), undated; 48938 (Box 139, Folder 5c)
  - Pond, Harry, undated; 48937 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Ponsonby, Henry Frederick, Sir (1825-1895), undated; 48936 (Box 139, Folder 5e)
  - Poole, Ernest: MSS. The Bandit Who Came Home [17 pp.]; The Fool Fox [26 pp.], undated; 48935 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Poole, John (1786-1872), undated; 48934 (Box 139, Folder 7a)
  - Poore, Benjamin Perley (1820-1887), undated; 48933 (Box 139, Folder 7b)
  - Pope, Jessie, undated; 48932 (Box 139, Folder 8a)
  - Porter, Anna Marie (1780-1852), undated; 48931 (Box 139, Folder 8b)
  - Porter, Gene Stratton (1863-1924), undated; 48930 (Box 139, Folder 8c)
  - Porter, Jane (1776-1850), undated; 48929 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Porter, Jane (1776-1850): Pictorial and Clips, undated; 48928 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Post, Melville D., undated; 48927 (Box 139, Folder 11a)
  - Potter, H. C., undated; 48926 (Box 139, Folder 11b)
  - Pound, Ezra, undated; 48925 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Powell, E.N., undated; 48924 (Box 139, Folder 13a)
  - Powell, Edward Alexander, undated; 48923 (Box 139, Folder 13b)
  - Powys, Llewlyn (1884-1939), undated; 48922 (Box 139, Folder 13c)
  - Powys, Theodore Francis (1875-1953): Correspondence, undated; 48921 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Powys, Theodore Francis (1875-1953): MS. All Fools Day, undated; 48920 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Powys, Theodore Francis (1875-1953): MS. Archdeacon Truggin; The Beautiful Flock; [see also Legal Size], undated; 48919 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Powys, Theodore Francis (1875-1953): MS. Dawn, undated; 48918 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Powys, Theodore Francis (1875-1953): MS. The White Paternoster, undated; 48917 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Paynter, Ambrose, undated; 48916 (Box 139, Folder 19a)
  - Pozner, Vladimir (1905- ), undated; 48915 (Box 139, Folder 19b)
  - Praed, Winthrop Mackworth (1802-1839), undated; 48914 (Box 139, Folder 19c)
  - Pratt, Sarah M. B., undated; 48913 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - Pratti, Alfred, undated; 48912 (Box 139, Folder 20a)
  - Prentice, George Denison (1802-1870), undated; 48911 (Box 139, Folder 20b)
  - Prescott, Harriet E., undated; 48910 (Box 139, Folder 20c)
  - Prescott, William Hickling (1796-1859), undated; 48909 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Price, Reynolds: Correspondence [1990], 48908 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Price, Reynolds: MS. Early Dark [a play], undated; 48907 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - Priestly, John Boynton (1894- ), undated; 48906 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Pringle, M. A., undated; 48905 (Box 139, Folder 24a)
  - Proctor, Adelaide Ann (1825-1864), undated; 48904 (Box 139, Folder 24b)
  - Procter, Bryan Waller (Barry Cornwall) (1787-1874), undated; 48903 (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Procter, Bryan Waller (Barry Cornwall) (1787-1874): MS., undated; 48902 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Prout, S., undated; 48901 (Box 139, Folder 27a)
  - [Provincetown Players: see Boxes 140-142], 1690-2000; 48900 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_e4f1f577e8e79aa3e42d4cd01acf0127)
  - Prowse, William Jeffrey (1836-1870), undated; 48899 (Box 139, Folder 27b)
  - Purdy, Richard L., undated; 48898 (Box 139, Folder 27c)
  - Purris, W., undated; 48897 (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - Putnam, E. S. C., undated; 48896 (Box 139, Folder 28a)
  - Putnam, George Palmer (1814-1872) [publisher], undated; 48895 (Box 139, Folder 28b)
  - Pyle, Howard, undated; 48894 (Box 139, Folder 28c)
  - Quaritch, Bernard Ltd. [firm], undated; 48893 (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - Quiller-Couch, Arthur, Sir (1863-1944), undated; 48892 (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Quin, Roger, undated; 48891 (Box 139, Folder 31a)
  - Quincy, J., undated; 48890 (Box 139, Folder 31b)
  - Provincetown Players: Correspondence to/from Susan Glaspell re History of Provincetown, undated; 48889 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Provincetown Players: Correspondence to/from Edna Kenton, undated; 48888 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Provincetown Players: Correspondence to Miss Robbins, Miss Ryan, Adolf Klauber, Blanche ___?, unknown, undated; 48887 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Provincetown Players: Cook, George Cram: T.M.s. The Founding of a Repertoire Theatre, undated; 48886 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Provincetown Players: Cook, George Cram: "The Way of the Group" [Little Theatre Review, Vol. 1, No.3, 1920], undated; 48885 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Provincetown Players: DeVoto, Bernard: "Minority Report" re O'Neill and Nobel Prize [The Saturday Review of Literature, Nov. 21, 1936], 48884 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Provincetown Players: Charles S. Gilpin and The Emperor Jones, undated; 48883 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Provincetown Players: Kenton, Edna: MS. The Story of... [1st draft. Uncorrected], undated; 48882 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Provincetown Players: Kenton, Edna: MS. The Provincetown Players...1915-1922 [pp. 1-55], undated; 48881 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Provincetown Players: Kenton, Edna: MS.2 The Provincetown Players...1915-1922 [pp.1-212, with gaps], undated; 48880 (Box 140.5, Folder 1)
  - Provincetown Players: Kenton, Edna: MS.3 The Provincetown Players... [carbon pp. 1-55, with gaps], undated; 48879 (Box 140.5, Folder 2)
  - Provincetown Players: Kenton, Edna: MS. Photocopies, undated; 48878 (Box 140.5, Folder 3)
  - Provincetown Players: O'Neill, Eugene: Biography/List of Plays, undated; 48877 (Box 140.5, Folder 4)
  - Provincetown Players: ___, Don: Seven Years; A.M.s. and T.M.s. with note to Eleanor Fitzgerald, undated; 48876 (Box 140.5, Folder 5)
  - Provincetown Players: The Story of a Woman's Adventure [unsigned synopsis], undated; 48875 (Box 140.5, Folder 6)
  - Provincetown Players: Third New York Season Announcement, 1918-19; 48874 (Box 140.5, Folder 7)
  - [folder number not assigned], 1690-2000; 48873 (Box 140.5, Folder 8)
  - Provincetown Players: Greenwich Playbill - Greenwich Village Theatre, 1924-26; 48872 (Box 140.5, Folder 9)
  - Provincetown Players: Recital Programs at Provincetown Players' Theatre-Club, undated; 48871 (Box 140.5, Folder 10)
  - Provincetown Players: Season of 1920-21 Announcement, 48870 (Box 140.5, Folder 11)
  - Provincetown Players: Season Program: In the Gariick Theatre [Season 1929-30], 48869 (Box 140.5, Folder 12)
  - [folder number not assigned], undated; 48868 (Box 140.5, Folder 13)
  - Provincetown Players: MS. Announcement of a Dark Season - 1922, 48867 (Box 140.5, Folder 14)
  - Provincetown Players: Photographs, undated; 48866 (Box 140.5, Folder 15)
  - Provincetown Players: Form Letters to Members and Subscribers, undated; 48865 (Box 140.5, Folder 16)
  - Provincetown Players: Lighting Used by Provincetown Playhouse, undated; 48864 (Box 140.5, Folder 17)
  - Provincetown Players: Membership Lists, 1916-1918; 48863 (Box 140.5, Folder 18)
  - Provincetown Players: Notice of Final Dress Rehearsal for Fiesta, by Michael Gold, 1929-1930; 48862 (Box 140.5, Folder 19)
  - Provincetown Players: Plan to Form Provincetown Players Corporation, undated; 48861 (Box 140.5, Folder 20)
  - Provincetown Players: Press Release, undated; 48860 (Box 140.5, Folder 21)
  - [folder number not assigned], undated; 48859 (Box 140.5, Folder 22)
  - Provincetown Players: Addenda The Cultural Moment...., undated; 48858 (Box 140.5, Folder 23)
  - Provincetown Players: Provincetown Playbill seasons 1923/24-1925/26, 1923-1926; 48857 (Box 140.5, Folder 24)
  - Provincetown Players: Newspaper Clippings: General [Legal Folders] [photocopies & originals], undated; 48856 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Provincetown Players: Newspaper Clippings: George Cram Cook [Legal Folders] [photocopies & originals], undated; 48855 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Provincetown Players: Newspaper Clippings: Susan Glaspell's The Verge [Legal Folders] [photocopies only], undated; 48854 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Provincetown Players: Newspaper Clippings: Michael Gold's Fiesta [Legal Folders] [photocopies only], undated; 48853 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Provincetown Players: Newspaper Clippings: Eugene O'Neill [Legal Folders] [photocopies & originals], undated; 48852 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Provincetown Players: Newspaper Clippings: Rudolph Schildkraut in Sholom Ash's Vengeance [Legal Folders], undated; 48851 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Provincetown Players: Scrapbook: Correspondence: Miscellaneous A-G, undated; 48850 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Provincetown Players: Scrapbook: Correspondence: Miscellaneous H-N, undated; 48849 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Provincetown Players: Scrapbook: Correspondence: Miscellaneous O-Z, undated; 48848 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Provincetown Players: Correspondence to Rhodes, Guy, undated; 48847 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Provincetown Players: Correspondence to Rogers, Arthur, undated; 48846 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Provincetown Players: Correspondence to, from, about Taylor, Tom, undated; 48845 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Rackham, Arthur (1867-1939), undated; 48844 (Box 143, Folder 1a)
  - Rae, Robert, undated; 48843 (Box 143, Folder 1b)
  - Raine, Kathleen (Jessie) (1908- ), undated; 48842 (Box 143, Folder 2a)
  - Raine, William MacLeod (1871- ), undated; 48841 (Box 143, Folder 2b)
  - Raleigh, Walter Alexander, Sir (1861-1922), undated; 48840 (Box 143, Folder 3a)
  - Randall, James Ryder (1839-1908), undated; 48839 (Box 143, Folder 3b)
  - Randolph, Sarah Nicholas (1839-1892), undated; 48838 (Box 143, Folder 3c)
  - Ranger, Henry Ward (1858-1916), undated; 48837 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Ransome, Arthur (1884-1967), undated; 48836 (Box 143, Folder 4a)
  - Rascoe, Burton (1892-1957), undated; 48835 (Box 143, Folder 4b)
  - Rathbone, Hannah Mary, undated; 48834 (Box 143, Folder 4c)
  - Ravogli, Giulia, undated; 48833 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Ray, Gordon, undated; 48832 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Read, Opie Percival (1852-1939), undated; 48831 (Box 143, Folder 6a)
  - Read, Thomas Buchanan (1822-1872), undated; 48830 (Box 143, Folder 6b)
  - Reade, Charles (1814-1884), undated; 48829 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Redgrave, Michael, Sir -1908, undated; 48828 (Box 143, Folder 8a)
  - Redmond, John Edward (1856-1918), undated; 48827 (Box 143, Folder 8b)
  - Reece, Robert (1838-1891), undated; 48826 (Box 143, Folder 8c)
  - Reeck, Emerich (Hyacinth Lehmann), undated; 48825 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Reed, Henry, undated; 48824 (Box 143, Folder 10a)
  - Reeve, Arthur B. (Arthur Benjamin) (1880-1936), undated; 48823 (Box 143, Folder 10b)
  - Reeve, Henry (1780-1814), undated; 48822 (Box 143, Folder 11a)
  - Reeve, Henry (1813-1895), undated; 48821 (Box 143, Folder 11b)
  - Reeve, Wybert, undated; 48820 (Box 143, Folder 12a)
  - Reeves, Helen Buckingham (Mathers) (1853-1920), undated; 48819 (Box 143, Folder 12b)
  - Reid, Grant, undated; 48818 (Box 143, Folder 13a)
  - Reid, Mayne, undated; 48817 (Box 143, Folder 13b)
  - Reid, Thomas, Sir (1842-1905), undated; 48816 (Box 143, Folder 13c)
  - [Reinhold, Robert: see Boxes 144 & 145], 1690-2000; 48815 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_650009095f9f789e0ec7b48570283527)
  - Remington, Frederic, undated; 48814 (Box 143, Folder 14a)
  - Repplier, Agnes, undated; 48813 (Box 143, Folder 14b)
  - Revell, Nellie, undated; 48812 (Box 143, Folder 15a)
  - Rexroth, Kenneth, undated; 48811 (Box 143, Folder 15b)
  - Reynolds, Paul, undated; 48810 (Box 143, Folder 15c)
  - Reynolds, Ernest Edwin (1894- ), undated; 48809 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Reynolds, Stephen, undated; 48808 (Box 143, Folder 15e)
  - Rhodes, James Ford (1848-1927), undated; 48807 (Box 143, Folder 16a)
  - Rice, Alice Hegan, undated; 48806 (Box 143, Folder 16b)
  - Rice, Cal Young (1872-1934), undated; 48805 (Box 143, Folder 16c)
  - Rice, Elmer (1892-1967), undated; 48804 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Rice, Wallace, undated; 48803 (Box 143, Folder 16e)
  - Richards, Alfred Bale (1820-1876), undated; 48802 (Box 143, Folder 17a)
  - Richards, E. Grant, undated; 48801 (Box 143, Folder 17b)
  - Richards, Laura E. (1850-1943), undated; 48800 (Box 143, Folder 17c)
  - Richardson, David Lester (1801-1943), undated; 48799 (Box 143, Folder 18a)
  - Richardson, Dorothy (1882- ), undated; 48798 (Box 143, Folder 18b)
  - Richardson, Henry Handel, undated; 48797 (Box 143, Folder 18c)
  - Richardson, Norval, undated; 48796 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Richardson, Samuel (1689-1761), undated; 48795 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Richmond, George (1809-1896), undated; 48794 (Box 143, Folder 20a)
  - Richmond, W. B., undated; 48793 (Box 143, Folder 20b)
  - Ricketts, Charles, undated; 48792 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Ridge, William Pett, undated; 48791 (Box 143, Folder 22a)
  - Ridgeway, William, Sir (1853-1926), undated; 48790 (Box 143, Folder 22b)
  - Ridpath, John Clark (1840-1900), undated; 48789 (Box 143, Folder 22c)
  - [Riesenberg, Felix: see Boxes 146 & 147], 1690-2000; 48788 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_5e2bc35026333b07828da6f2fd76684f)
  - Riis, Jacob (1849-1914), undated; 48787 (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Riley, James Whitcomb (1849-1916), undated; 48786 (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Ring, D., undated; 48785 (Box 143, Folder 24a)
  - Ripley, George (1803-1880), undated; 48784 (Box 143, Folder 24b)
  - [Ritchie, Anne: see Box 148], 1690-2000; 48783 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_32436ad8c8772f8ed25b44edc581ae32)
  - Rives, Hallie Erminie (1876- ), undated; 48782 (Box 143, Folder 24c)
  - Robbins, Leonard Harman (1877- ), undated; 48781 (Box 143, Folder 24)
  - Roberts, Charles George Douglas, Sir, undated; 48780 (Box 143, Folder 25)
  - Roberts, Kenneth, undated; 48779 (Box 143, Folder 26a)
  - Roberts, M., undated; 48778 (Box 143, Folder 26b)
  - Robert, Michael, undated; 48777 (Box 143, Folder 26c)
  - Roberts, Morley, undated; 48776 (Box 143, Folder 27)
  - Roberts, Morley: MS. R.L.S. [Robert Louis Stevenson], undated; 48775 (Box 143, Folder 28)
  - Robertson, John, undated; 48774 (Box 143, Folder 29a)
  - Robertson, John Henry (1909-1965) (John Connell, pseud.), undated; 48773 (Box 143, Folder 29b)
  - Robertson, William, undated; 48772 (Box 143, Folder 29c)
  - Robins, Elizabeth, undated; 48771 (Box 143.5, Folder 1a)
  - Robins, Elizabeth: MS. Whither and How, undated; 48770 (Box 143.5, Folder 1b)
  - Robins, Elizabeth: MS. Whither and How, undated; 48769 (Box 143.5, Folder 1c)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, undated; 48768 (Box 143.5, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, John Richard, Sir, undated; 48767 (Box 143.5, Folder 1e)
  - Robinson, Lennox, undated; 48766 (Box 143.5, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, Rowland Evans, undated; 48765 (Box 143.5, Folder 1g)
  - Robinson, Thomas Romney, undated; 48764 (Box 143.5, Folder 1h)
  - Robson, Flora, undated; 48763 (Box 143.5, Folder 2a)
  - Roche, Arthur Somers, undated; 48762 (Box 143.5, Folder 2b)
  - Roche, Paul: MS. With Duncan Grant in Turkey, undated; 48761 (Box 143.5, Folder 3)
  - Rockwell, Norman, undated; 48760 (Box 143.5, Folder 4)
  - [Rodolitz, Gerald: see Box 149], 1690-2000; 48759 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_f0eeee202bef3b838987e27c4df8bdad)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Benefactor [pp. 1-2, Map], undated; 48758 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Benefactor [Book 1, Chapters 1-3], undated; 48757 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Benefactor [Book 1, Chapters 4-7], undated; 48756 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Benefactor [Book 2], undated; 48755 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Benefactor [Book 3, pp. 460-615], undated; 48754 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Benefactor [Book 3, pp. 616-748], undated; 48753 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Benefactor [Book 3, 749-790], undated; 48752 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Graffiti and Meatballs, undated; 48751 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Reinhold, Robert: Correspondence, undated; 48750 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Five Fitts, Part I, undated; 48749 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Five Fitts, undated; 48748 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Five Fitts, undated; 48747 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Lifeguard, undated; 48746 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. The Lifeguard, undated; 48745 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Nero and Fool, undated; 48744 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Nero and Fool, undated; 48743 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Nuclear Hecuba, undated; 48742 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Reinhold, Robert: MS. Poems, undated; 48741 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Reinhold, Robert: Flyers and Map, undated; 48740 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Reinhold, Robert: Notices, undated; 48739 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Reinhold, Robert: Newspaper Clippings, undated; 48738 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. Mother Sea, Book I, undated; 48737 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. Mother Sea, Book II, undated; 48736 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. Mother Sea, Book III, undated; 48735 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. Mother Sea, Book IV, undated; 48734 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. The Pacific Ocean, Chapters 1-9, undated; 48733 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. The Pacific Ocean, Chapters 10-24, undated; 48732 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. The Pacific Ocean [discards?], undated; 48731 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. Portrait of New York, Chapters 1-4, undated; 48730 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Riesenberg, Felix: MS. Portrait of New York, Chapters 5-10, undated; 48729 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Addison, William; Bell, MacKenzie; Bidder, Mrs., undated; 48728 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Brookfield; Browning; Mrs. Buck, undated; 48727 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence: Chapman; Christie; Chrimpton, Lady; 3 A.L.s., undated; 48726 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Cornford (envelope only); Dobie; Dyer, undated; 48725 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Mr. & Mrs. Saville-Clark, undated; 48724 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Ewing; Faithfull; Fitzgerald; Fletcher, undated; 48723 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Gilder; Goshen; Grove, undated; 48722 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Halsey, F. W.; Hannay; Hoskyu, undated; 48721 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Jefferson; Johnson; Jones; Litchfield, undated; 48720 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence: M, undated; 48719 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence: P, undated; 48718 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray (1837-1919): Correspondence to Robins, Elizabeth [photocopies: originals in Robins Papers], undated; 48717 (Box 148, Folder 12)